# SM

## Sundeep Mistry

ASPIRING SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- 07944107710
- mistrysundeep@gmail.com
- 231 The Vale, London, NW118TN
- LinkedIn
- % My Portfolio

### ABOUT ME

Junior developer with 5+ months of experience implementing REST APIs in Python using the FastAPI framework; some exposure to docker and PostgreSQL. I've worked with monolithic systems but have a clear understanding of microservices. With passion and ambition, I'm ready to jump into the next challenge.

#### SKILLS

**PYTHON** 



**POSTGRESQL** 



HTML



**JAVASCRIPT** 



VCS



#### EDUCATION

Open Degree BSc - 2:2

The Open University

April 2018 – April 2022

Computer Science Games BSc

*Brighton University*September 2015 – July 2017

Computer Science (Level 3 BTEC)

Stanmore College
September 2013 – September 2015

#### EXPERIENCE

Junior Developer Iprism Underwriting / June 2022 – November 2022

Working in a small team updating an old system into a webified version using Python 3.10 and the FastAPI framework to create REST APIs to gather data on different aspects of insurance policies and proposals gathered by underwriters.

- Use of version control to share code with my manager and other team members
- Effective debugging and communication with team about issues or queries with
  tasks.
- Understanding and use of Oauth2 security and query parameterization.

#### Part-Time Tutor FunTech / Remote / April 2021 – December 2021

Working remotely with students aged 5-16 teaching Python, HTML and SQL going from fundamentals to more complex concepts such as algorithms and responsive web design.

- Effective communication with management team on the lessons
- Debugging and troubleshooting software problems during the lessons

Part-Time Tutor Explore Learning / London and remote / August 2018 – April 2021

Working in center with groups of up to 6 students between ages 4-14 on math and English topics.

- Using verbal and visual methods to demonstrate the topic being worked on
- Running additional content classes such as 11+ and creative writing
- Effective communication with parents on concerns or progress of a student
- Online and in-center technical support during sessions